<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joe Zeng</title>
    <description>Software and Sports</description>
    <link>http://blog.joezeng.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.joezeng.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 23:46:32 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 23:46:32 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Invites and Lessons Learned</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks back I finished writing out my first major feature at Kik. The feature is called invites and allows users to share bots that they find on our platform with their friends. More on the feature &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.kik.com/2016/07/07/invite-friends-bot-experiences-kik/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. It has only been out for a couple weeks but is already producing some very encouraging results and I’m very excited to see where bot developers take this feature!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some lessons learned:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Protocol buffers are awesome and really help to define schemas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Architecting code is very important and following consistent design patterns can prevent a lot of headaches&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MVP/MVVM help a lot in seperating business logic and view logic, and make for easy testing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reactive programming really helps define streams of data and ends up simplifying a lot of business logic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.joezeng.me/invites/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.joezeng.me/invites/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About Me</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! I’m a computer science student at the University of Waterloo going into my third year of study. This summer, I’m interning at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kik.com/&quot;&gt;Kik Interactive&lt;/a&gt;, working on their chat bot platform. I am an avid tennis player and rock climber and love following basketball (although ball is definitely not life). I’m going to try and document bits of my life here so stay tuned :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://blog.joezeng.me/about/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.joezeng.me/about/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
